<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Stackmate India</title>
    <link>https://stackmate.in/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Stackmate India</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stackmate.in/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetski Account Recovery</title>
      <link>https://stackmate.in/blog/2021/02/jetski-account-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stackmate.in/blog/2021/02/jetski-account-recovery/</guid>
      <description>In this post we will use the bdk-cli tool to recover a Jetski 2/3 multi-sig account. This would be useful in the unlikely event of downtime at Stackmate.
 recover your seed&amp;rsquo;s extended master key and derive child account keys create a PSBT to unlock your unspent bitcoin sign and finalize the resulting PSBTs broadcast and confirm spending transactions via Blockstream  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solo Account Recovery</title>
      <link>https://stackmate.in/blog/2021/02/solo-account-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stackmate.in/blog/2021/02/solo-account-recovery/</guid>
      <description>This tutorial is a stripped down version of Steve Myers and Thundabirds article from bdk-cli
 In this post we will use the bdk-cli tool to recover accounts from a bitcoin seed.
 recover your seed&amp;rsquo;s extended master key and derive child account keys create a PSBT to unlock your unspent bitcoin sign and finalize the resulting PSBTs broadcast and confirm spending transactions via Blockstream  Note: We use testnet in the examples for you to try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots</title>
      <link>https://stackmate.in/blog/2021/01/roots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stackmate.in/blog/2021/01/roots/</guid>
      <description>Origins A bitcoin hodler, a bitcoin miner and a bitcoin developer met. Vision A sound monetary base. Process Work with the larger bitcoin-core community to develop bitcoin infrastructure and build relavant products that improve UX while preserving bitcoin-core fundamentals. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>